# WESTON VANDERPOOL

Humboldt, KS 66748 • (620) 253-4964 • <u>westonvanderpool@gmail.com</u> • <u>https://wesvpool.github.io</u>

# **Professional Summary**

Recipient of a Professional Certificate in Coding from MIT. Multi-talented and experienced manager with over 5 years of consistently being rewarded for success in planning and operational improvements. Experience in policy development and staff management procedures positively impacting overall morale and productivity. Excellent reputation for resolving problems, improving customer satisfaction, and driving overall operational improvements.

# Skills

- Shopify
- Liquid
- HTML
- JavaScript
- CSS
- MERN Stack
- Able to work in a fast-paced environment
- Excellent communication skills
- Strong computer background

- Very quick learner
- Strong attention to detail
- Team building
- · Brand building
- Cost analysis and savings
- Customer assistance
- Testing and troubleshooting
- Budget coordination
- Account development

#### Education

## Massachusetts Institute of Technology – 2022

Professional Certificate in Coding: Full Stack Development With MERN

https://wes-vanderpoolfullstackbankapp.herokuapp.com/#/

# **Work History**

## Shopify Freelancer/Web Developer, 05/2022 to Current

https://www.f5customrods.com

- 9+ Projects completed
- Transform the client's vision to reality
- Optimize site layouts
- Site Management
- Full store setup
- Work within Liquid to provide customized functions

# Service Advisor, 09/2021 to 05/2022

Steve Faulkner Ford - Chanute, KS

- Schedule customer service appointments
- Be point of contact for customers
- Write repair orders
- Provide estimates and advise of needed repairs or maintenance
- Ensure timely repairs by managing part arrival and technician workload

## Custom Rod Builder/Shipping Associate, 06/2019 to 03/2021

F5 Custom Rods – Oklahoma City, OK

• Hand craft custom fishing rods to the specifics of the customer.

- Use attention to detail to ensure that minute details are correct
- Interact with customers on various social media platforms.
- Ensure accurate, timely, and safe packaging for shipping on all rod and merchandise orders.

# Warehouse Inventory Manager, 06/2018 to 05/2019

# MOC Central USA – Oklahoma City, OK

- Maximized coverage by carefully allocating resources, setting schedules and delegating assignments to delivery drivers.
- Strengthened inventory processes to balance supply needs with budget and space limitations.
- Inspected work areas for cleanliness and obstacles and removed cartons and boxes to keep work areas organized and hazard-free.
- Collaborated with sales team members to stay current on inventory levels, complete accurate orders and resolve item issues.
- Accepted delivered packages, verified products and checked delivery totals to keep system records current and accurate.
- Completed voluntary physical inventory counts each month and complete Inventory count every 5-6 months.
- Troubleshooting and repair of machines used for removing/flushing vehicle fluids with MOC products.

## Branch Manager, 01/2017 to 06/2018

# Hertz Rent A Car - Oklahoma City, OK

- Resolved escalated customer issues in timely manner, which boosted retention rates.
- Enhanced branch production rates by handling staff conflicts, evaluations, hiring/termination processes, coaching employees on company protocol.
- Boosted branch sales by developing and deepening customer loyalty through incentive programs.
- Engaged employees in business processes with positive motivational techniques.
- Identified and capitalized on community business opportunities with effective networking.
- Uncovered and resolved strategic and tactical issues impacting sales management and business operations.
- Maintained confidentiality of bank records and client information to prevent mishandling of data and potential breaches.
- Protected company assets with strategic risk management approaches.

## Service Drive Manager/Service Advisor, 04/2016 to 12/2016

# Bob Howard Nissan - Oklahoma City, OK

- Supervises hourly employees on service drive.
- Insures cleanliness and professional appearance of service drive.
- Monitors processes and procedures
- Schedule vehicle service appointments
- Greet customers
- Write repair orders
- Be point of contact for customers
- Process customer payments
- Perform customer follow-up to ensure customer satisfaction and to remind them of upcoming maintenance needed.

#### **Service Advisor**, 11/2013 to 03/2016

## Jim Norton Toyota Of OKC – Oklahoma City, OK

- Schedule vehicle service appointments
- Greet customers
- Write repair orders
- Be point of contact for customers
- Process customer payments

- Perform customer follow-up to ensure customer satisfaction and to remind them of upcoming maintenance needed
- Completed Toyota Service Professional certification, 2014
- From February 2015 to October 2015, had gross sales greater than \$65,000 more than the next ranked advisor.